O.W. Riegel Papers WLU.Coll.0387
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- Journalism Department, 1932-1974; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 8.8 Linear Feet This series is primarily contained in large and medium size archival storage boxes. Additionally, there are two boxes of Newspaper Clippings related to the Lee Memorial Journalism Foundation and other aspects of th
  - Correspondence, 1932-1974 (Box 1-2, Folder 12-185)
    - American Press Society Min-Rut, 1932-1974 (Folder 28)
    - American Press Society Sou-Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 29)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers- Andrews C., 1932-1974 (Folder 30)
    - Andrews R.- Apple, 1932-1974 (Folder 31)
    - Applications, 1932-1974 (Folder 32)
    - Arm-Ash, 1932-1974 (Folder 33)
    - ASNE-Atk, 1932-1974 (Folder 34)
    - A Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 35)
    - Bac-Bas, 1932-1974 (Folder 36)
    - Bat-Ben, 1932-1974 (Folder 37)
    - Ber-Bel, 1932-1974 (Folder 38)
    - Beu-Bli, 1932-1974 (Folder 39)
    - Boa-Boo, 1932-1974 (Folder 40)
    - Booth, 1932-1974 (Folder 41)
    - Bor-Bot, 1932-1974 (Folder 42)
    - Bou-Bre, 1932-1974 (Folder 43)
    - Bri-Bro, 1932-1974 (Folder 44)
    - Brown, 1932-1974 (Folder 45)
    - Bryan-Bryant, 1932-1974 (Folder 46)
    - Buchanan, 1932-1974 (Folder 47)
    - Buck-Byr; B Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 48)
    - Cam-Can, 1932-1974 (Folder 49)
    - Cantril, 1932-1974 (Folder 50)
    - Capel, 1932-1974 (Folder 51)
    - Car-Cas, 1932-1974 (Folder 52)
    - Cat-Cham, 1932-1974 (Folder 53)
    - Chan-Cla, 1932-1974 (Folder 54)
    - Cle-Cli, 1932-1974 (Folder 55)
    - Coa-Coc, 1932-1974 (Folder 56)
    - Colburn, 1950-1959 (Folder 57)
    - Colburn, 1960-1962 (Folder 58)
    - Cole-Coleman C., 1932-1974 (Folder 59)
    - Coleman H., 1932-1974 (Folder 60)
    - Coleman R.-Con, 1932-1974 (Folder 61)
    - Cook-Cope L., 1932-1974 (Folder 62)
    - Cope M., 1932-1974 (Folder 63)
    - Copen-Cote, 1932-1974 (Folder 64)
    - Council for Democracy, 1932-1974 (Folder 65)
    - Council on Foreign Relations- Cso, 1932-1974 (Folder 66)
    - Cun-Cut, 1932-1974 (Folder 67)
    - C Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 68)
    - Dabney, 1932-1974 (Folder 69)
    - Dar-Dau, 1932-1974 (Folder 70)
    - Ded-Del, 1932-1974 (Folder 71)
    - Den-DeW, 1932-1974 (Folder 72)
    - Die-Dur; D Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 73)
    - Eas-Edw, 1932-1974 (Folder 74)
    - Efa-Enr, 1932-1974 (Folder 75)
    - Equiptment 1001-Fore, 1932-1974 (Folder 76)
    - Equiptment Gli-Meg, 1932-1974 (Folder 77)
    - Equiptment Mon-Wri; Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 78)
    - Ern-Exp, 1932-1974 (Folder 79)
    - Fan-Far, 1932-1974 (Folder 80)
    - Fau-Fis, 1932-1974 (Folder 81)
    - Fit-Fow, 1932-1974 (Folder 82)
    - Fra-Fre, 1932-1974 (Folder 83)
    - French Journalists, 1932-1974 (Folder 84)
    - Frei-Fure, 1932-1974 (Folder 85)
    - Gai-Gar, 1932-1974 (Folder 86)
    - Gee-Gil, 1932-1974 (Folder 87)
    - Gro-Glass C., 1932-1974 (Folder 88)
    - Glass P., 1932-1974 (Folder 89)
    - Gle-Goo, 1932-1974 (Folder 90)
    - Gor-Gro, 1932-1974 (Folder 91)
    - Guild, 1932-1974 (Folder 92)
    - Gut-Gwy, 1932-1974 (Folder 93)
    - Hoa-Ham, 1932-1974 (Folder 94)
    - Han, 1932-1974 (Folder 95)
    - Har-Hev, 1932-1974 (Folder 96)
    - Hic-Hob, 1932-1974 (Folder 97)
    - Hodges, 1932-1974 (Folder 98)
    - Hof-Hoo, 1932-1974 (Folder 99)
    - Hop-How, 1932-1974 (Folder 100)
    - Hub-Hyn, 1932-1974 (Folder 101)
    - Ide-Inauguration, 1932-1974 (Folder 102)
    - International Association of Mass Communication Research Bou-Kay, 1932-1974 (Folder 103)
    - International Association of Mass Communication Research Nix-Swi, 1932-1974 (Folder 104)
    - International Association of Mass Communication Research Terrou, 1932-1974 (Folder 105)
    - International Association of Mass Communication Research Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 105)
    - International Paper Company-Its, 1932-1974 (Folder 106)
    - Jac-Jen, 1932-1974 (Folder 107)
    - Jobs Bak-Ham, 1950 (Folder 108)
    - Jobs Hob-Pur, 1950 (Folder 109)
    - Jobs Ric-Win; Misc., 1950 (Folder 110)
    - Jobs Agn-Col, 1950-1951 (Folder 111)
    - Jobs Cra-Lit, 1950-1951 (Folder 112)
    - Jobs McN-Ste; Misc., 1950-1951 (Folder 113)
    - Jobs Arp-Cha, 1952-1953 (Folder 114)
    - Jobs Cor-Har, 1952-1953 (Folder 115)
    - Jobs Has-Mar, 1952-1953 (Folder 116)
    - Jobs McK-Rob, 1952-1953 (Folder 117)
    - Jobs Row-Ste, 1952-1953 (Folder 118)
    - Jobs Tur-Woo; Misc., 1952-1953 (Folder 119)
    - Jobs, 1956-1964 (Folder 120)
    - John, 1932-1974 (Folder 121)
    - Jones, 1932-1974 (Folder 122)
    - Jor-Jud, 1932-1974 (Folder 123)
    - Kan-Kel, 1932-1974 (Folder 124)
    - Kem-Kinn, 1932-1974 (Folder 125)
    - Kint-Kub; Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 126)
    - Labro, 1932-1974 (Folder 127)
    - Lac-Lea, 1932-1974 (Folder 128)
    - LeB-Lew, 1932-1974 (Folder 129)
    - Leyburn, 1932-1974 (Folder 130)
    - Lim-Lon, 1932-1974 (Folder 131)
    - Lov-Lyo, 1932-1974 (Folder 132)
    - L Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 133)
    - Mac-Man, 1932-1974 (Folder 134)
    - Mapel, 1932-1974 (Folder 135)
    - Mar-May, 1932-1974 (Folder 136)
    - McA-McM, 1932-1974 (Folder 137)
    - Mea-Merc, 1932-1974 (Folder 138)
    - Mergenrather, 1932-1974 (Folder 139)
    - Mes-Min, 1932-1974 (Folder 140)
    - Moe-Mon, 1932-1974 (Folder 141)
    - Moo-Mye; Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 142)
    - Nag-New, 1932-1974 (Folder 143)
    - Newspapers in 1952 Forecast, 1942 (Folder 144)
    - Nie-Nos, 1932-1974 (Folder 145)
    - O, 1932-1974 (Folder 146)
    - Pai-Pen, 1932-1974 (Folder 147)
    - Per-Prie, 1932-1974 (Folder 148)
    - Princeton Listening Center, 1939-1940 (Folder 149)
    - Princton Listening Center Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 150)
    - Pub-Qui, 1932-1974 (Folder 151)
    - Rac-Rei, 1932-1974 (Folder 152)
    - Ren-Rob, 1932-1974 (Folder 153)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1932-1974 (Folder 154)
    - Rom-Rut, 1932-1974 (Folder 155)
    - Sae-Sch, 1932-1974 (Folder 156)
    - Science Service, 1940-1947 (Folder 157)
    - Science Service, 1948 (Folder 158)
    - Science Service, 1949-1951 (Folder 159)
    - Science Service, 1952-1953 (Folder 160)
    - Science Service, 1954-1974 (Folder 161)
    - Sciu-Smi, 1932-1974 (Folder 162)
    - SNPA, 1931-1938 (Folder 163)
    - SNPA, 1939-1941 (Folder 164)
    - SNPA, 1946-1949 (Folder 165)
    - SNPA, 1950-1953 (Folder 166)
    - SNPA, 1954-1974 (Folder 167)
    - Sny-Spea, 1932-1974 (Folder 168)
    - Speech, 1932-1974 (Folder 169)
    - Spi-Sto, 1932-1974 (Folder 170)
    - Str-Sup; Misc, 1932-1974 (Folder 171)
    - United Nations-University of Toronto, 1932-1974 (Folder 173)
    - U.P. Radio Newswire, 1932-1974 (Folder 174)
    - Urc-Ust, 1932-1974 (Folder 175)
    - Val-Vin, 1932-1974 (Folder 176)
    - Virginia Press Association, 1932-1974 (Folder 177)
    - Voi-Vol, 1932-1974 (Folder 178)
    - Wad-War, 1932-1974 (Folder 179)
    - Was-Wee, 1932-1974 (Folder 180)
    - Wei-Wee, 1932-1974 (Folder 181)
    - Wil-Wri, 1932-1974 (Folder 182)
    - Yal-Zie, 1932-1974 (Folder 183)
    - Zilahy, 1932-1974 (Folder 184)
    - Misc., 1947-1974 (Folder 185)
  - Course Materials, 1932-1974 (Box 3-7, Folder 186-372, Box 11-13, Folder 508-520)
    Items in this subseries relate to the courses within the Journalism Department which Riegel taught while at Washington and Lee University. Courses ranged in topic from public opinion to advertising to psychological warfare and propaganda. Most courses are sorted by order of sylabbi, class handouts, lecture notes, and other relevant materials to the course. The Psychological Warfare and Propaganda course also has a few student samples of a project where students were to make their own propaganda aimed at countries behind the Iron Curtain.
    - Journalism 101, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 186-189)
      The Journalism 101 course focused on the principles of Journalism. Within this subseries are documents related to the course including syllabi, class handouts, quizzes, exams, and other materials Riegel had that were relevant to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1932-1974 (Folder 186)
      - Handouts, 1932-1974 (Folder 187)
      - Assessment, 1932-1974 (Folder 188)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 189)
    - Journalism 102, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 190-198)
      Journalism 102 was a course that covered the principles of Journalism, and at times was a continuation of Journalism 101 to create a year long class. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, quizzes, exams, lecture notes and other material Riegel had that was relevant to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1932-1974 (Folder 190)
      - Handouts, 1932-1974 (Folder 191)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1931-1939 (Folder 192)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1940-1963 (Folder 193)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1931-1937 (Folder 194)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1937-1966 (Folder 195)
      - Assessment: Quizzes Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 196)
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Folder 197)
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Folder 198)
    - Journalism 106--Public Opinion, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 199-203)
      Riegel's public oppinion course focused on the purpose and manner of polling, specifically as a pulse of American Democracy. It elaborated on how to conduct polls and how they influence and show the views of the public. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, lecutre notes, and other related materials.
      - Syllabi & Assessment, 1932-1974 (Folder 199)
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Folder 200)
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Folder 201)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 202)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 203)
    - Journalism 107--Literary Criticism, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 204-214)
      Riegel's Literary Critism course focused on the purpose and manner in which one critiques a written work. Riegel emphasized the different critical theories by different reviewers and had students study reviewers and conduct their own reviews using the fundamentals taught in the course. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, quizzes, exams, lecture notes, and other material related to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1932-1974 (Folder 204)
      - Handouts, 1932-1974 (Folder 205)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1931-1942 (Folder 206)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1931-1941 (Folder 207)
      - Lecture Notes: Reviewers, 1932-1974 (Folder 208)
      - Lecture Notes: Criticism & Critics, 1932-1974 (Folder 209)
      - Lecture Notes: Historical Criticism, 1932-1974 (Folder 210)
      - Lecture Notes: Symbolism and Art Forms, 1932-1974 (Folder 211)
      - Lecture Notes: Criticism & Obscenity, 1932-1974 (Folder 212)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 213)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 214)
    - Journalism 111--Principles of Journalism, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Journalism 112, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Journalism 113--Short Story Writing, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 217-223)
      The Journalism Department's Short Story Writing Course focused on the elements of a short story and its goal of portraying life as the author sees it from their own lens. within the course, students were expected to anaylze and uncover the principles of short story writing and apply them in their own works. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, quizzes, exams, and other materials related to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1932-1974 (Folder 217)
      - Handouts, 1932-1974 (Folder 218)
      - Assessment, 1931-1933 (Folder 219)
      - Lecture Notes: History & Point of View, 1932-1974 (Folder 220)
      - Lecture Notes: History, 1932-1974 (Folder 221)
      - Lecture Notes: Themes, Plans, & Characterization, 1932-1974 (Folder 222)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 223)
    - Journalism 116, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Journalism 201--Principles of Advertising, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 225-226)
      The Principles of Advertising course covered basic elements of advertisements found in mass media sources. Items in this subseries consist of a course syllabus, quizzes, and exams.
      - Syllabi & Quizzes, 1932-1974 (Folder 225)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1932-1974 (Folder 226)
    - Journalism 202, 1932-1974 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Journalism 213--Law, 1932-1974 (Box 3-4, Folder 228-273)
      The Journalism Department's course on communications law focused on the legal developments regarding the freedom of the press. Course topics ranged from copyright, to libel, to privacy, to climate, to the Freedom of Information Act, and courtroom procedures. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, extensive lecture notes sorted by topic, and extensive relevant materials related to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1932-1974 (Folder 228)
      - Handouts, 1968-1971 (Folder 229)
      - Assessment, 1964-1968 (Folder 230)
      - Lecture Notes: Intro, 1932-1974 (Folder 231)
      - Lecture Notes: Broadcasting, 1932-1974 (Folder 232)
      - Lecture Notes: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 233)
      - Lecture Notes: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 234)
      - Lecture Notes: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 235)
      - Lecture Notes: Freedom of Information Act, 1932-1974 (Folder 236)
      - Lecture Notes: Freedom of Information Act, 1932-1974 (Folder 237)
      - Lecture Notes: Courts and Procedure, 1932-1974 (Folder 238)
      - Lecture Notes: Courts and Procedure, 1932-1974 (Folder 239)
      - Lecture Notes: Libel, 1932-1974 (Folder 240)
      - Lecture Notes: Libel, 1932-1974 (Folder 241)
      - Lecture Notes: Privacy, 1932-1974 (Folder 242)
      - Lecture Notes: Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 243)
      - Student Work, 1932-1974 (Folder 244)
      - Background Material: Intro, 1932-1974 (Folder 245)
      - Background Material: Intro, 1932-1974 (Folder 246)
      - Background Material: Intro, 1932-1974 (Folder 247)
      - Background Material: Intro, 1932-1974 (Folder 248)
      - Background Material: Broadcasting, 1932-1974 (Folder 249)
      - Background Material: Broadcasting, 1932-1974 (Folder 250)
      - Background Material: Broadcasting, 1932-1974 (Folder 251)
      - Background Material: Broadcasting, 1932-1974 (Folder 252)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 253)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 254)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 255)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 256)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 257)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 258)
      - Background Material: Climate, 1932-1974 (Folder 259)
      - Background Material: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 260)
      - Background Material: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 261)
      - Background Material: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 262)
      - Background Material: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 263)
      - Background Material: Copy Right, 1932-1974 (Folder 264)
      - Background Material: Freedom of Information Act, 1932-1974 (Folder 265)
      - Background Material: Freedom of Information Act, 1932-1974 (Folder 266)
      - Background Material: Freedom of Information Act, 1932-1974 (Folder 267)
      - Background Material: Courts & Procedure, 1932-1974 (Folder 268)
      - Background Material: Libel, 1932-1974 (Folder 269)
      - Background Material: Privacy, 1932-1974 (Folder 270)
      - Background Material: Privacy, 1932-1974 (Folder 271)
      - Background Material: Trial by Newspaper, 1932-1974 (Folder 272)
      - Background Material Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 273)
    - Journalism 221--Psychological Warfare and Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Box 4-5, Folder 274-327, Box 1-3)
      The Psychological Warfare and Propaganda course covered how the media has been used to sway public opinion in a variety of settings. Students examined the methods the military, governments, intelligence agencies, international U.S. broadcasts, and other sources used in an attempt to persuade others to support their goals and causes. Items in ths subseries consist of student work on a couple of projects including a mock propaganda piece by Philippe Labro, course syllabi, class handouts and project rubrics, lecutre notes, and other materials related to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1952-1957 (Folder 274)
      - Syllabi, 1958-1962 (Folder 275)
      - Syllabi, 1962-1965 (Folder 276)
      - Syllabi, 1966-1972 (Folder 277)
      - Syllabi Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 278)
      - Handouts: General, 1932-1974 (Folder 279)
      - Handouts: Course Reading, 1932-1974 (Folder 280)
      - Handouts: Newspaper & Propaganda Analysis, 1932-1974 (Folder 281)
      - Handouts: Political Warfare Project, 1932-1974 (Folder 282)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1939-1959 (Folder 283)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1960-1966 (Folder 284)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1967-1972 (Folder 285)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1939-1959 (Folder 286)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1960-1966 (Folder 287)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1967-1972 (Folder 288)
      - Assessment: Quizzes Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 289)
      - Lecture Notes: Propaganda Objectives: Division, 1932-1974 (Folder 290)
      - Lecture Notes: Propaganda Objectives: Division, 1932-1974 (Folder 291)
      - Lecture Notes: Propaganda Objectives: Conversion, 1932-1974 (Folder 292)
      - Lecture Notes: Propaganda Objectives: Conversion, 1932-1974 (Folder 293)
      - Lecture Notes: Submission, Consolidation, & Counter Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Folder 294)
      - Lecture Notes: Russia, 1932-1974 (Folder 295)
      - Lecture Notes: Russia, 1932-1974 (Folder 296)
      - Lecture Notes: CIA & China, 1932-1974 (Folder 297)
      - Lecture Notes: U.S. Policy, 1932-1974 (Folder 298)
      - Lecture Notes: U.S. Policy, 1932-1974 (Folder 299)
      - Lecture Notes: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 300)
      - Lecture Notes: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 301)
      - Lecture Notes: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 302)
      - Lecture Notes: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 303)
      - Lecture Notes: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 304)
      - Lecture Notes: Finale, 1932-1974 (Folder 305)
      - Lecture Notes: Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 306)
      - Student Work, 1932-1974 (Folder 307)
      - Student Work, 1932-1974 (Folder 308)
      - Background Material: Russia, 1932-1974 (Folder 309)
      - Background Material: Russia, 1932-1974 (Folder 310)
      - Background Material: Russia, 1932-1974 (Folder 311)
      - Background Material: China, 1932-1974 (Folder 312)
      - Background Material: CIA, 1932-1974 (Folder 313)
      - Background Material: CIA, 1932-1974 (Folder 313)
      - Background Material: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 314)
      - Background Material: Military, 1932-1974 (Folder 315)
      - Background Material: USA, 1932-1974 (Folder 316)
      - Background Material: USA, 1932-1974 (Folder 317)
      - Background Material: Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Folder 318)
      - Background Material: Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Folder 319)
      - Background Material: Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Folder 320)
      - Background Material: Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Folder 321)
      - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 322)
      - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 323)
      - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 324)
      - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 325)
      - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 326)
      - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 327)
      - Lecture Notes: Russia, 1932-1974 (Box 1)
      - Lecture Notes: Russia, 1932-1974 (Box 2)
      - Lecture Notes: Misc., 1932-1974 (Box 3)
    - Journalism 222--Public Relations, 1932-1974 (Box 5-7, Folder 328-356, Box 4-5)
      The Public Relations course focused on the purposes of public relations and the various attitudes people hold towards the field. Students were tasked to analyze the goals of a person in a public relations position and to understand why some view it as a means for corruption while others see it as an essential part of any business, firm, or public figure. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, lecture notes, and other material related to the course.
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Box 4)
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Box 5)
      - Syllabi, 1962-1973 (Folder 328)
      - Syllabi Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 329)
      - Syllabi Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 330)
      - Handouts: Reading List, 1932-1974 (Folder 331)
      - Handouts: Projects, 1932-1974 (Folder 332)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1947-1962 (Folder 333)
      - Assessment: Final Exam, 1963-1972 (Folder 334)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1957-1962 (Folder 335)
      - Assessment: Quizzes, 1964-1973 (Folder 336)
      - Lecture Notes: Intro & Media, 1932-1974 (Folder 337)
      - Lecture Notes: Mass Media & Propaganda, 1932-1974 (Folder 338)
      - Lecture Notes: Communication & Publicity, 1932-1974 (Folder 339)
      - Lecture Notes: Politics, 1932-1974 (Folder 340)
      - Lecture Notes: Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 341)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 342)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 343)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 344)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 345)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 346)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 347)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 348)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 349)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 350)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 351)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 352)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 353)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 354)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 355)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 356)
    - Journalism 225--Advertising, 1932-1974 (Folder 357)
    - Journalism 226--Advertising, 1932-1974 (Box 7, Folder 358-365)
      This advertising course focused on the principles and critical analysis of advertisements. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, lecture notes, and other material related to the course.
      - Syllabi & Handouts, 1932-1974 (Folder 358)
      - Assessment, 1932-1974 (Folder 359)
      - Lecture Notes: Growth & Development--Twin Targets, 1932-1974 (Folder 360)
      - Lecture Notes: History of Advertising, 1932-1974 (Folder 361)
      - Lecture Notes: Successful Ads, 1932-1974 (Folder 362)
      - Lecture Notes: Advertising Aspects, 1932-1974 (Folder 363)
      - Lecture Notes: Types of Ads, 1932-1974 (Folder 364)
      - Background Material, 1932-1974 (Folder 365)
    - Journalism 241--Advanced Reporting, 1932-1974 (Folder 366)
    - Journalism 243--The Editorial, 1932-1974 (Box 7, Folder 367-371)
      The Editorial was a journalism department course that focused on the principles and practice of newspaper editorial writing. Students in the course were members of a hypothetical editorial board and were tasked to develop articles on a variety of topics. Items in this subseries consist of course syllabi, class handouts, lecture notes, and other material related to the course.
      - Syllabi, 1932-1974 (Folder 367)
      - Assessment & Handouts, 1932-1974 (Folder 368)
      - Lecture Notes, 1932-1974 (Folder 369)
      - Misc. Notes, 1932-1974 (Folder 370)
      - Assignment Binder, 1959-1960 (Folder 371)
    - Misc., 1932-1974 (Folder 372)
    - Handbooks, 1933-1959 (Box 11, Folder 508)
    - Handbooks, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 509)
    - Journalism 221, 1966-1970 (Box 11, Folder 510)
    - Journalism 224, 1954-1957 (Box 11, Folder 511)
    - Journalism 235, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 512)
    - Journalism 236, 1962-1971 (Box 11, Folder 513)
    - Journalism 321, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 514)
    - Journalism 335, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 515)
    - Journalism 336, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 516)
    - Journalism 336, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 517)
    - Roll Books, 1967-1973 (Box 12, Folder 518)